The average worldwide commute is around 40 minutes.
全球平均通勤时间约为40分钟。
But UK workers are travelling 54 minutes and Londoners commute approximately 80 minutes by car and over two hours by train every day, according to the UK Department of Transport.
但据英国交通部数据，英国上班族每天通勤54分钟，伦敦人开车通勤约80分钟，乘火车则超过两小时。
Drawing on all that travelling experience, what can these commuters teach us about how best to behave during all that time spent in cars, trains, and buses?
凭借这些通勤经验，这些在汽车、火车和公交车上度过那么多时间的通勤者，在如何规范行为上有什么可以教我们的呢？
First of all, travel etiquette is important.
首先，通勤礼仪很重要。
A recent BBC article asked its readers to describe which of their fellow commuters' actions constituted bad manners.
最近的一篇文章中，BBC请读者们描述同行通勤者的哪些行为不太礼貌。
Top answers included talking too loudly, eating stinky food and putting feet up on the seats.
最常见的回答包括大声喧哗、吃有异味的食物和把脚放在座位上。
Several respondents even mentioned a fellow train passenger clipping their toenails in the carriage.
几位受访者甚至提到有乘客在车厢里剪脚趾甲。
Their reactions to this boorish behaviour included feeling disgusted, perplexed and appalled.
他们对这种粗鄙行为的反应包括感到厌恶、困惑和震惊。
A more controversial activity is doing make-up.
更具争议的行为是化妆。
Opinions varied on whether this was impolite or inconsiderate.
关于这是否不礼貌或不顾及他人，人们意见不一。
One reader said he was so offended by this conduct, he had to change carriages.
一位读者说，他对这种行为感到非常不适，不得不换车厢。
However, the idea that make-up should be applied in private is an outdated concept, says professional make-up artist Nic Chapman and one half of beauty brand, Pixiwoo.
然而，专业化妆师、美妆品牌Pixiwoo创始人之一尼克・查普曼（Nic Chapman）表示，“化妆应在私下进行”的观念已过时。
"We are not ashamed of wearing make-up," she told the BBC.
“我们不羞于化妆，”她告诉BBC。
Dilruba Khanom told the BBC "I do admire a woman's confidence to not give two hoots and slap on the face."
迪鲁巴・哈诺姆（Dilruba Khanom）则对BBC说：“我十分欣赏那些毫不介意、大胆化妆的女性的自信。”
But a long commute isn't just about negative experiences.
但漫长的通勤并不全是负面体验。
Many UK commuters turned to innovative activities to better make use of their time on transport.
许多英国通勤者通过创新活动更好地利用通勤时间。
37-year-old Ben Yallop, who manages international judicial relations at the Royal Courts of Justice, used his daily three-hour trip to write and self-publish two novels.
37岁的本・亚洛普（Ben Yallop）在皇家法院负责国际司法关系工作，他每天利用三小时通勤时间写作并自费出版了两部小说。
He started "jotting down ideas" for a series of them.
他开始为一系列小说“记录想法”。
"I've done almost all my research, plotting and writing on the train," he tells the BBC.
“我几乎所有的研究、构思和写作都是在火车上完成的，”他告诉BBC。
Alternatively, 24-year-old Amy Dickett uses her 90-minute trip to photograph fellow commuters for her Commute Blog.
24岁的艾米・迪基特（Amy Dickett）则利用90分钟通勤时间为她的《通勤博客》拍摄同行通勤者。
She snaps a picture and asks them to tell her something surprising about themselves.
她拍下照片，让他们分享自己的奇闻趣事。
"Usually they are surprised but glad to have some entertainment on an otherwise boring journey.
“通常他们会感到惊讶，但很高兴在枯燥的旅途中有这样的娱乐。
Often the people around us join in and will ask their own questions," she told the BBC.
周围的人也常常加入进来，提出自己的问题，”她告诉BBC。
So, no matter where or how long your journey is, take a leaf from the UK commuter's book.
因此，无论你在哪里或旅程多长，都可以借鉴英国通勤者的经验。
Don't antagonise your fellow passengers and rather than staring into space – use your time creatively.
不要激怒同行乘客，与其发呆——不如创造性地利用时间。